<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Dogecoin.org</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Dogecoin.org</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://dogecoin.org/pt/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How can I become a Dogecoin developer?</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/blog/becoming-a-dogecoin-developer/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://dogecoin.org/pt/blog/becoming-a-dogecoin-developer/</guid><description>Dogecoin is an open-source project, meaning that anyone with some technical know-how can contribute to Dogecoin’s technical development. Even if you’re new to the space, it’s never too late to learn new tricks!
Dogecoin has an amazing team of developers and volunteers who are committed to welcoming new people into the space and helping them to learn and develop their skills. The community is extremely encouraging, too, and it’s very common to see old Shibes helping new Shibes as they enter the space.</description></item><item><title>How Does Dogecoin Work?</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/blog/how-does-dogecoin-work/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://dogecoin.org/pt/blog/how-does-dogecoin-work/</guid><description>Magic and memes! (Just kidding. Kind of.)
First things first: Dogecoin is money.
Like other popular cryptocurrencies, Dogecoin works by utilising blockchain technology. Unlike a lot of other popular cryptocurrencies, though, the fees to send Dogecoin are extremely small, and the speed by which Dogecoin transactions are confirmed is relatively fast.
Simply put, if you would like to send money to someone who is located anywhere in the world — or receive money from someone who is located anywhere in the world — without using a centralised bank and paying foreign currency exchange and transfer fees, then Dogecoin can work for you!</description></item><item><title>What is a mining pool?</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/blog/what-is-a-mining-pool/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://dogecoin.org/pt/blog/what-is-a-mining-pool/</guid><description>Mining pools are services, operated by third parties not affiliated with Dogecoin, which allow a group of miners to combine their hashing power when attempting to solve the &amp;ldquo;puzzles&amp;rdquo; involved in mining Dogecoin.
Mining rewards - consisting of 10,000 Dogecoin per block plus transaction fees associated to the transactions included in the block - are awarded to the miner who discovers a valid Proof of Work for a new block before any other miner in the network.</description></item><item><title>How can I help?</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/blog/how-can-i-help-doge/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://dogecoin.org/pt/blog/how-can-i-help-doge/</guid><description>There are so many ways to get involved and support Dogecoin. From making memes and artworks – to educating people who are new to crypto: there are endless possibilities for you to get involved and to help the Dogecoin movement.
A good place to start is by joining one or more of the highly active communities on platforms such as Reddit, Twitter, and Discord.
If you have a technical background and would like to contribute to Dogecoin technical development, you can get involved via Dogecoin Core and The Dogecoin Foundation GitHub repositories.</description></item><item><title>What is a blockchain?</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/blog/what-is-a-blockchain/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://dogecoin.org/pt/blog/what-is-a-blockchain/</guid><description>A blockchain is a digital distributed ledger that is used as a system for validating and recording transaction information. This digital ledger of transactions is duplicated and distributed throughout an entire network of computers connected to the blockchain.
The Dogecoin blockchain consists of thousands of computers – called nodes – meaning that transaction information is not stored in one centralised place. Instead, Dogecoin blockchain information is stored across thousands of nodes.</description></item><item><title>What is a wallet, really?</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/blog/what-is-a-wallet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://dogecoin.org/pt/blog/what-is-a-wallet/</guid><description>A wallet is a set of private keys that gives you access to the control of certain coins on the blockchain ledger. When you spend a coin, control of that coin is transferred from being controlled by your keys to being controlled by someone else&amp;rsquo;s keys.
A wallet app (often referred to simply as a &amp;ldquo;wallet&amp;rdquo;) is an application which manages these keys, reports these amounts, and facilitates the transfer of amounts of coins between addresses.</description></item><item><title>What merchants currently accept Dogecoin?</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/blog/merchants-accepting-doge/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://dogecoin.org/pt/blog/merchants-accepting-doge/</guid><description>At the time of writing, there is a rapidly expanding list of merchants who accept Dogecoin as a form of payment. Because of this, finding — and maintaining — an up-to-date directory of businesses that #AcceptDoge is no small feat!
Thanks to the overwhelming support from the Dogecoin community in encouraging — and then promoting — businesses that accept Dogecoin, we anticipate that the list of businesses that accept Dogecoin is only going to grow much larger and cover a variety of industries and sectors in the years to come.</description></item><item><title>Who are the current Dogecoin developers?</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/blog/dogecoin-developers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://dogecoin.org/pt/blog/dogecoin-developers/</guid><description>The development of Dogecoin is open, permissionless, and participatory. Over the years, a varied group of developers has contributed to the development of Dogecoin Core, Dogecoin&amp;rsquo;s reference implementation.
Dogecoin was created by Billy Markus and Jackson Palmer in 2013. Billy worked on Dogecoin Core as its main developer for its first releases. Dogecoin Core started as a fork of Lucky Coin and Litecoin, themselves forks of Bitcoin Core. Dogecoin Core thus derived most of its codebase from the work Bitcoin developers had done on the Bitcoin repository.</description></item></channel></rss>