<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Much-start-codings on Dogecoin.org</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/much-start-coding/</link><description>Recent content in Much-start-codings on Dogecoin.org</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://dogecoin.org/pt/much-start-coding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GigaWallet</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/much-start-coding/gigawallet/contents/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://dogecoin.org/pt/much-start-coding/gigawallet/contents/</guid><description>Some more text here</description></item><item><title>GigaWallet</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/much-start-coding/gigawallet/install/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://dogecoin.org/pt/much-start-coding/gigawallet/install/</guid><description>Soon There are multiple ways to install GigaWallet.
Download &amp;amp; Changelog: Always Recommended to download from GitHub latest release GigaWallet for bug free and latest features.
Visit the releases page to view the changelog.
Stable release Grab from GigaWallet Important Note: Make sure you grab from the source.
Using The Command Line: Debian/Ubuntu sudo apt-get install ....... MacOS sudo apt-get install .......</description></item><item><title>GigaWallet</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/much-start-coding/gigawallet/introduction/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://dogecoin.org/pt/much-start-coding/gigawallet/introduction/</guid><description>The Dogecoin GigaWallet is a backend service which provides a convenient integration API for platforms such as online shops, exchanges, social media platforms etc, to transact Dogecoin on behalf of their users.
The purpose of the GigaWallet is to allow the rapid uptake of Dogecoin as a payment option, by taking the complexity and risk out of integrating Dogecoin payments.
DogeConnect: Payment Protocol The DogeConnect JSON protocol for authorising Dogecoin transactions via interaction with a user&amp;rsquo;s wallet on their device is a key part of the GigaWallet project.</description></item><item><title>LibDogecoin</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/much-start-coding/libdogecoin/contents/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://dogecoin.org/pt/much-start-coding/libdogecoin/contents/</guid><description>Some more text here</description></item><item><title>LibDogecoin</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/much-start-coding/libdogecoin/install/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://dogecoin.org/pt/much-start-coding/libdogecoin/install/</guid><description>Quick start There are multiple ways to install LibDogecoin.
Download &amp;amp; Changelog: Always Recommended to download from GitHub latest release LibDogecoin for bug free and latest features.
Visit the releases page to view the changelog.
Stable release Grab from LibDogecoin Important Note: Make sure you grab from the source.
Using The Command Line: Debian/Ubuntu sudo apt-get install autoconf automake libtool build-essential libevent-dev MacOS xcode_select --install sudo chown -R $(whoami) $(brew --prefix)/*</description></item><item><title>LibDogecoin</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/much-start-coding/libdogecoin/introduction/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://dogecoin.org/pt/much-start-coding/libdogecoin/introduction/</guid><description>What is Libdogecoin? Libdogecoin will be a complete implementation of the Dogecoin Protocols, as a C library (and series of bindings to popular languages) which will allow anyone to build a Dogecoin compliant product, without needing to worry about the deeper, complicated specifics of the crypto functions. Libdogecoin is here to make crypto development simple, clean, and fun!
This will be a pure library, providing a set of callable functions to implement in external projects, but not a ‘runnable’ node facility.</description></item></channel></rss>