<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Such-dogecoin-projects on Dogecoin.org</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/such-dogecoin-projects/</link><description>Recent content in Such-dogecoin-projects on Dogecoin.org</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://dogecoin.org/pt/such-dogecoin-projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dogecoin Core</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/such-dogecoin-projects/dogecoin-core/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://dogecoin.org/pt/such-dogecoin-projects/dogecoin-core/</guid><description>What is Dogecoin? Dogecoin is a community-driven cryptocurrency that was inspired by a Shiba Inu meme. The Dogecoin Core software allows anyone to operate a node in the Dogecoin blockchain networks and uses the Scrypt hashing method for Proof of Work. It is adapted from Bitcoin Core and other cryptocurrencies.</description></item><item><title>ShibeShip</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/such-dogecoin-projects/shibeship/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://dogecoin.org/pt/such-dogecoin-projects/shibeship/</guid><description>What is SibeShip? Its a Opensource MarketPlace where anyone can buy and sell anything using Dogecoin. Powerd by GigaWallet and LibDogecoin.</description></item><item><title>GigaWallet</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/such-dogecoin-projects/gigawallet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://dogecoin.org/pt/such-dogecoin-projects/gigawallet/</guid><description>The Dogecoin GigaWallet is a backend service which provides a convenient integration API for platforms such as online shops, exchanges, social media platforms etc, to transact Dogecoin on behalf of their users.
The purpose of the GigaWallet is to allow the rapid uptake of Dogecoin as a payment option, by taking the complexity and risk out of integrating Dogecoin payments.
DogeConnect: Payment Protocol The DogeConnect JSON protocol for authorising Dogecoin transactions via interaction with a user&amp;rsquo;s wallet on their device is a key part of the GigaWallet project.</description></item><item><title>LibDogecoin</title><link>http://dogecoin.org/pt/such-dogecoin-projects/libdogecoin/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://dogecoin.org/pt/such-dogecoin-projects/libdogecoin/</guid><description>What is Libdogecoin? Libdogecoin will be a complete implementation of the Dogecoin Protocols, as a C library (and series of bindings to popular languages) which will allow anyone to build a Dogecoin compliant product, without needing to worry about the deeper, complicated specifics of the crypto functions. Libdogecoin is here to make crypto development simple, clean, and fun!
This will be a pure library, providing a set of callable functions to implement in external projects, but not a ‘runnable’ node facility.</description></item></channel></rss>